turkishseries.li 2017-06-14

# Privacy Policy | TurkishSeries.Li

We Welcome you to TurkishSeries **.Li**. We always value your privacy. It is extremely important to us. With this Privacy Policy, we aim to let you know everything about the information we collect from you, how we use it and why we don’t share it with anyone.

**Kind of Information We Collect from You :  
**  
We only collect your personal information when you take certain actions to make it known, like registering, making purchases, authenticating or interacting with members. Until you don’t make yourself known to us, you will be able to use our content and services anonymously.

**When You Browse the Website** – When you are at our website, we may collect some log data. This may include the type of browser and operating system you use, address of internal or external page that initially referred you, your IP address and all the pages on our website that you visit with your IP address. This is just limited information we collect to diagnose any issues with the website.

With this information, we are able to assess your suggestion. We will also ask about some other details including your name, URL and email. However, these fields are just optional and we ask for this information to give you appropriate credit. If you don’t want us to use this information, we will not publish your name with your suggestion. Moreover, we will never spam your email.

**When You Sign up for a Newsletter** – When you sign up or subscribe to our Newsletter, we will ask you for your email address. This will allow us to send you the day’s projects and all the relevant information you might need. We will not use your email address for any other purpose than to send the Newsletter. Until you unsubscribe, you will stay on our list. You can unsubscribe anytime you want.

When You Communicate Directly with Us – If you try to communicate with us directly through emails or other mediums of communication, we will retain your information. This will allow us to respond quickly to your request. We will keep this information with us indefinitely. This way, we will have a history of our previous correspondence.

**Collection of Information using Cookies** – This one is quite basic. Since advertising pays our bills, we use cookies.

**Public Information :**

Whenever you submit some information as public, you give us the authority to share it publicly. For instance, you may choose to make certain information publicly available. This may include your bio, photos, email, alias and so on. Certain areas of the website, like discussion forums and comment threads are also viewable by other visitors on the website. When you wish to share this information publicly, you need to understand that anyone may use, access and disclose this information.

**Who Do We Share Your Information With :**

We do not share, rent or sell your personal info to anyone, except when there is need for legal response. We will just use your information to operate and constantly improve our services. We also use your information to communicate with you, fulfill your requests, conduct research and personalize the advertisements and content provided by you.

**Links to Other Websites** – It is very important to understand that our website contains numerous links to other websites. These websites are not controlled or owned by us. You need to be aware that we are not responsible in any way for the privacy policies and practices of other websites.

**Data Security** – We have always used high-end physical, technical and administrative procedures to protect your personal and confidential data. However, despite our numerous measures, data can still be lost.

**Changes to the Privacy Policy :**

Our Privacy Policy may be revised at any time. If there are any significant changes to our Privacy Policy, we will make them available on the website.

**Our Cookie Policy :**

We use cookies on our website. You need to understand that online publishing is supported by advertising. The same is true for our website. Until someone finds a better way to advertise, we will have to use cookies. Cookies lay the foundation for advertising, and advertising pays for our website.

**What is a Cookie?**

Cookies are very small data files that are stored in your hard drive by websites. Cookies have a unique ID associated with your internet browser. Crowded uses cookies for analytics. It lets us know about your activity on the website. Cookies are also used to display advertisements based on your specific interests.

Besides this, we also display sharing buttons to help you share information and items on social networking websites like Twitter, Facebook and so on. However, your interactions and communications will be protected by the Privacy Policy of the websites governing these sharing buttons, and not by this Privacy Policy.
